Social Justice Center; Records apap177
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1987-1997; 3; 2.3 cubic ft.
  - SELFHELP Crafts, Educational Materials, Philippines, Sri Lanka, 1991; Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - SELFHELP Crafts, Educational Materials, South and Central America, 1990; 1992; Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - SELFHELP Crafts, Educational Materials, Thailand, West Bank, 1986; 1990; 1994; Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - SELFHELP Crafts, Mailings, Fliers, 1992-1995; Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - SELFHELP Crafts, Newsletter, 1990-1992 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - SELFHELP Crafts, Newsletter, 1993-1996 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Unidentified Photographs, 1993 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Unidentified Photographs, Negative, Slides, Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Bowl For Peace, Hanging Signs, Undated (Flat-file 1)
  - Bowl For Peace, Hanging Signs, Undated (Flat-file 2)
  - Bowl For Peace, Hanging Signs, Undated (Flat-file 3)
  - Bowl For Peace, Hanging Signs, Undated (Flat-file 4)
  - Korea, Im Su Kyung, Posters, Undated (Flat-file 5)
  - Korea, Im Su Kyung, Posters, Undated (Flat-file 6)
  - National Abortion and Reproductive Rights Action League, Poster, Undated (Flat-file 7)
  - Rape Crisis Center, Protest Signs, Undated (Flat-file 8)
  - Unidentified, Protest Signs, Undated (Flat-file 9)